(Leonard:)But just for fun... why?
(Penny:)Not in a rush, busy with work...
(Penny:)Things are good
right now.
Really good.
(Leonard:)You still want
to get married, right?
(Penny:)Oh, my God. Yes.
Why would you even ask that?
(Raj:)I don't know.
Because we don't have a date?
(Penny:)Well, you want a date,
pick a date.
(Leonard:)It's not just the date.
(Leonard:)We haven't talked
about anything.
(Leonard:)Big wedding, small wedding,
indoor, outdoor...
(Sheldon:)Outdoor? Oh.
I can RSVP no right now.
(Penny:)Okay, indoor it is.
Big or small?
(Leonard:)Is your dad paying for it?
I doubt it.
(Leonard:)Okay, two friends each.
(Penny:)All right, well,
I want it in a church.
(Leonard:)Fine. I want black-tie.
(Leonard:)Fine.
I want to release butterflies.
(Sheldon:)Seriously? Airborne worms?
Okay. Well, then it's settled:
(Leonard:)small indoor church wedding,
black-tie, no butterflies.
(Penny:)Sounds perfect.
Great.
(Leonard:)You still
didn't pick a date.
Stay out of it!
Shut up!